<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Is it Vegan?</string>
    <string name="search_view_hint">Search ingredients</string>
    <string name="ingredient_key" translatable="false">INGREDIENT_KEY</string>
    <string name="ingredient_name_placeholder">Ingredient name</string>
    <string name="ingredient_e_number_placeholder" translatable="false">E123</string>
    <string name="ingredient_information_placeholder">Information</string>
    <string name="ingredient_information_empty">No information</string>
    <string name="action_camera">Open camera</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="setting_theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="setting_language_app">App</string>
    <string name="theme_entries_system">System theme</string>
    <string name="theme_entries_light">Light</string>
    <string name="theme_entries_dark">Dark</string>
    <string name="preference_category_language">Language</string>
    <string name="preference_category_ui">Display</string>
    <string name="preference_category_info">Information</string>
    <string name="setting_language_ingredients">Ingredient names</string>
    <string name="language_app_entries_system">System language</string>
    <string name="language_ingredients_entries_app">Use app language</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_text">Hi! My name is Jeroen and I developed this app during the first months after I decided that I wanted to adapt a vegan lifestyle. I found it annoying to browse websites in the store to find out whether products were vegan or not. With this app, I hope to support others in their quest for an animal-friendly lifestyle. \n\nA list like this will never be finished nor flawless. If you miss information or find an error, please let me know by sending an email to contactisitvegan@gmail.com.</string>
    <string name="title_scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="scan_hint">Point your device at the product\'s ingredient list</string>
    <string name="error_opening_browser">Error opening browser</string>
    <string name="title_search_online">Search online</string>
    <string name="share_message">Let me recommend you this application! 🌱</string>
    <string name="button_share">Share this app</string>
    <string name="button_clear">Clear list</string>
    <string name="error_no_camera_permission_granted">Feature requires camera permission</string>

    <!-- Ingredients -->
    <string name="ingredient_potassium_inosinate">Potassium inosinate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_disodium_5_ribonucleotides">Disodium 5\'-ribonucleotides</string>
    <string name="ingredient_disodium_inosinate">Disodium inosinate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_agar">Agar, agar-agar</string>
    <string name="ingredient_angora_wool">Angora wool</string>
    <string name="ingredient_gum_arabic">Gum arabic</string>
    <string name="ingredient_ascorbate">Ascorbate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_ascorbic_acid">Ascorbic acid, vitamin C</string>
    <string name="ingredient_ascorbyl_palmitate">Ascorbyl palmitate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_astaxanthin">Astaxanthin</string>
    <string name="ingredient_eggplant">Eggplant</string>
    <string name="ingredient_bone_char">Bone char</string>
    <string name="ingredient_beeswax">Beeswax</string>
    <string name="ingredient_butter_fat">Butter fat</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cocoa_butter">Cocoa butter, cacao butter</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cocoa_mass">Cocoa mass</string>
    <string name="ingredient_calcium_5_ribonucleotides">Calcium 5\'-ribonucleotides</string>
    <string name="ingredient_calcium_ascorbate">Calcium ascorbate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_calcium_formate">Calcium formate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_calcium_guanylate">Calcium guanylate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_calcium_inosinate">Calcium inosinate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_calcium_lactate">Calcium lactate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_casein">Casein, caseinate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_castoreum">Castoreum</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cera_alba">Cera alba</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cera_flava">Cera flava</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cholic_acid">Cholic acid</string>
    <string name="ingredient_citranaxanthin">Citranaxanthin</string>
    <string name="ingredient_collagen">Collagen</string>
    <string name="ingredient_egg">Egg</string>
    <string name="ingredient_egg_yolk">Egg yolk</string>
    <string name="ingredient_gelatin">Gelatin</string>
    <string name="ingredient_glycerol">Glycerol, glycerine</string>
    <string name="ingredient_guanosine_monophosphate">Guanosine monophosphate, GMP</string>
    <string name="ingredient_guanylic_acid">Guanylic acid</string>
    <string name="ingredient_hemp">Hemp</string>
    <string name="ingredient_honey">Honey</string>
    <string name="ingredient_inosine_monophosphate">Inosine monophosphate, IMP</string>
    <string name="ingredient_inosinic_acid">Inosinic acid</string>
    <string name="ingredient_potassium_ascorbate">Potassium ascorbate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_potassium_guanylate">Potassium guanylate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_potassium_lactate">Potassium lactate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_potassium_nitrate">Potassium nitrate, saltpetre</string>
    <string name="ingredient_carmine">Carmine, cochineal</string>
    <string name="ingredient_buttermilk">Buttermilk</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cashmere">Cashmere</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cotton">Cotton</string>
    <string name="ingredient_keratin">Keratin</string>
    <string name="ingredient_coconut_fiber">Coconut fiber</string>
    <string name="ingredient_l_cysteine">L-Cysteine</string>
    <string name="ingredient_l_cystine">L-Cystine</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lactitol">Lactitol</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lactobacillus">Lactobacillus</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lactose">Lactose</string>
    <string name="ingredient_latex">Latex</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lecithin">Lecithin, lecithins</string>
    <string name="ingredient_linen">Linen</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lyocell">Lyocell</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lysozyme">Lysozyme, muramidase</string>
    <string name="ingredient_milk">Milk</string>
    <string name="ingredient_powdered_milk">Powdered milk, dried milk</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lactic_acid">Lactic acid</string>
    <string name="ingredient_formic_acid">Formic acid, methanoic acid</string>
    <string name="ingredient_modal">Modal</string>
    <string name="ingredient_mono__and_diglycerides_of_fatty_acids">Mono- and diglycerides of fatty acids</string>
    <string name="ingredient_musk">Musk</string>
    <string name="ingredient_sodium_ascorbate">Sodium ascorbate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_sodium_formate">Sodium formate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_disodium_guanylate">Disodium guanylate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_sodium_lactate">Sodium lactate</string>
    <string name="ingredient_sodium_nitrite">Sodium nitrite</string>
    <string name="ingredient_nisin">Nisin</string>
    <string name="ingredient_pearls">Pearls</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lard">Lard</string>
    <string name="ingredient_schellac">Schellac</string>
    <string name="ingredient_skatole">Skatole</string>
    <string name="ingredient_soybeans">Soybeans</string>
    <string name="ingredient_soy_lecithin">Soy lecithin</string>
    <string name="ingredient_tallow">Tallow</string>
    <string name="ingredient_vanilla">Vanilla</string>
    <string name="ingredient_violoxanthin">Violoxanthin</string>
    <string name="ingredient_vitamin_b12">Vitamin B12, cobalamin</string>
    <string name="ingredient_vitamin_d2">Vitamin D2, ergocalciferol</string>
    <string name="ingredient_vitamin_d3">Vitamin D3, cholecalciferol</string>
    <string name="ingredient_whey_protein">Whey protein</string>
    <string name="ingredient_whey">Whey</string>
    <string name="ingredient_whey_powder">Whey powder</string>
    <string name="ingredient_wool">Wool</string>
    <string name="ingredient_wool_fat">Wool fat, lanolin</string>
    <string name="ingredient_zeaxanthin">Zeaxanthin</string>
    <string name="ingredient_seaweed">Seaweed</string>
    <string name="ingredient_silk">Silk</string>
    <string name="ingredient_sunflower_lecithin">Sunflower lecithin</string>
    <string name="ingredient_potassium_inosinate_info">Potassium inosinate is a potassium salt of inosinic acid. Inosinic acid is a substance that occurs naturally in both plants and animals and plays a role in the metabolism of cells. It is used as a flavor enhancer in foods. Inosinic acid is often added to savory products such as stock cubes, ready-to-eat noodles and chips. Inosinic acid can be isolated from meat and fish, but can also be produced in a vegan way. Major producers have indicated that they use vegan-produced inosinic acid.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_disodium_5_ribonucleotides_info">Disodium 5\'-ribonucleotides is a mixture of calcium salts of guanylic and insinic acid. Both of these are often produces in a vegan way.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_disodium_inosinate_info">Disodium inosinate is a disodium salt of inosinic acid. Inosinic acid is a substance that occurs naturally in both plants and animals and plays a role in the metabolism of cells. It is used as a flavor enhancer in foods. Inosinic acid is often added to savory products such as stock cubes, ready-to-eat noodles and chips. Inosinic acid can be isolated from meat and fish, but can also be produced in a vegan way. Major producers have indicated that they use vegan-produced inosinic acid.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_agar_info">Agar, or agar-agar, is a jelly-like substance, obtained from red algae. It is often used as a substitute for gelatin.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_angora_wool_info">Angora wool is a soft fibre that comes from the domestic Angora rabbit. Soft, warm sweaters are made from this material.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_gum_arabic_info">Gum arabic is a product of trees. It is a resinous gum that is released when the bark of the tree is damaged. Gum arabic is commonly used as a glazing agent and was previously used as a glue.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_ascorbate_info">Ascorbates are salts derived from ascorbic acid (vitamin C). Ascorbic acid is a natural acid, present in almost all fruits and vegetables. It is obtained commercially by bacterial fermentation of glucose followed by a chemical oxidation step. Ascorbic acid is used as an anti-oxidant and bread improver.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_ascorbic_acid_info">Ascorbic acid (vitamin C) is a natural acid, present in almost all fruits and vegetables. It is obtained commercially by bacterial fermentation of glucose followed by a chemical oxidation step. Ascorbic acid is used as an anti-oxidant and bread improver.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_ascorbyl_palmitate_info">Ascorbyl palmitate is a combination of ascorbic acid (vitamin C) and palmitic acid (a normal fatty acid obtained from fat, almost always vegan). Ascorbyl palmitate is an anti-oxidant in fatty products. It is mainly used to protect oils with a lot of unsaturated fatty acids against rancidity.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_astaxanthin_info">Astaxanthin is naturally found in microalgae, yeast, certain fish and crustaceans, and in the feathers of certain bird species. Artificial petroleum products are used to make astaxanthin. Astaxanthin is used to give food a pink color.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_eggplant_info">Despite its name, eggplants do not actually contain eggs. They thank their name due to their shape. Eggplants are vegan.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_bone_char_info">Bone char is an animal charcoal. It is made by heating bones.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_beeswax_info">Beeswax, cera alba or cera flava, is wax made by bees. It is used in candy, cosmetics and candles.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_butter_fat_info">Butterfat is the fat in dairy. It is the natural constituent of cows\' milk and it is used to make butter.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cocoa_butter_info">Cocoa butter, or cacao butter, is the fat contained in cocoa beans.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cocoa_mass_info">Cocoa mass is a product obtained from cocoa beans, the seed of the cocoa tree. It is an important raw material for chocolate.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_calcium_5_ribonucleotides_info">Calcium 5\'-ribonucleotides is a mixture of calcium salts of guanylic and insinic acid. Both of these are often produces in a vegan way.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_calcium_ascorbate_info">Calcium ascorbate is the calcium salt of ascorbic acid (vitamin C). Ascorbic acid is a natural acid, present in almost all fruits and vegetables. It is obtained commercially by bacterial fermentation of glucose followed by a chemical oxidation step. Ascorbic acid is used as an anti-oxidant and bread improver.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_calcium_formate_info">Calcium formate is obtained commercially from calcium hydroxide and carbon monoxide and used as a preservative in, for example, fruit juice.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_calcium_guanylate_info">Calcium guanylate is a guanylic acid. Guanylic acid is a building block of RNA, an important component in the functioning of living cells and is found in animals, plants and bacteria. It is used as a flavor enhancer in foods. Guanylic acid is often added to savory products such as stock cubes, ready-to-eat noodles and crisps. Guanylic acid can be isolated from sardines, but can also be produced in a vegan way from yeast. Major producers have indicated that they use vegan-produced guanylic acid.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_calcium_inosinate_info">Calcium inosinate is a calcium salt of inosinic acid. Inosinic acid is a substance that occurs naturally in both plants and animals and plays a role in the metabolism of cells. It is used as a flavor enhancer in foods. Inosinic acid is often added to savory products such as stock cubes, ready-to-eat noodles and chips. Inosinic acid can be isolated from meat and fish, but can also be produced in a vegan way. Major producers have indicated that they use vegan-produced inosinic acid.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_calcium_lactate_info">Calcium lactate is the calcium salt of lactic acid. It is a natural acid produced by lactic acid bacteria in fermented products. Calcium lactate is commercially produced by bacterial fermentation of molasses or starch. Lactic acid and lactates are used as preservatives. It strengthens the structure of vegetables, fruit and potatoes during processing. It is also an anti-oxidant. Calcium lactate is used in cream, cheese, ice cream, soup and baking powder, among other things.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_casein_info">Casein is an animal protein in cow\'s milk. It is used in the form of caseinate in the food industry.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_castoreum_info">Castoreum comes from beaver scent glands and is used as a flavoring in foods and cigarettes and as a fragrance in perfumes.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cera_alba_info">Beeswax, cera alba or cera flava, is wax made by bees. It is used in candy, cosmetics and candles.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cera_flava_info">Beeswax, cera alba or cera flava, is wax made by bees. It is used in candy, cosmetics and candles.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cholic_acid_info">Cholic acid is a natural part of the bile of vertebrates. Although it can also be produced synthetically, it is mainly extracted from bovine bile.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_citranaxanthin_info">Citranaxanthin is a carotenoid pigment used as a food additive. There are natural sources of citranaxanthin, but it is generally prepared synthetically. It is used as an animal feed additive to impart a yellow color to chicken fat and egg yolks.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_collagen_info">Collagen is gelatin before hydrolysis takes place. Gelatin is a protein obtained by boiling skin, tendons, ligaments and bones with water. Collagen is often used in beauty products and joint medications.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_egg_info">Eggs are not considered vegan.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_egg_yolk_info">Egg yolk comes from eggs and is therefore not vegan.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_gelatin_info">Gelatin is a protein obtained by boiling skin, tendons, ligaments, and bones with water. It is usually obtained from cows or pigs. Gelatin is used in cosmetics; as a thickener for puddings; in candies, cakes, ice cream, and yogurts; on photographic film; in vitamins as a coating and as capsules, and it is sometimes used to assist in “clearing” wines.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_glycerol_info">Glycerol, or Glycerine, is a colorless sugar alcohol. It is a natural constituent of fats, both natural and vegetable. Glycerol is mainly extracted during the production of biodiesel, but sometimes also from animal fat. The substance is used in paint, cosmetics, food, perfume and explosives, among others. Most manufacturers cannot properly identify the source. In practice, glycerol usually appears to come from a vegetable source.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_guanosine_monophosphate_info">Guanylic acid, or guanosine monophosphate (GMP), is a building block of RNA, an important component in the functioning of living cells, and is found in animals, plants and bacteria. It is used as a flavor enhancer in foods. Guanylic acid is often added to savory products such as stock cubes, ready-to-eat noodles and crisps. Guanylic acid can be isolated from sardines, but can also be produced in a vegan way from yeast. Major producers have indicated that they use vegan-produced guanylic acid.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_guanylic_acid_info">Guanylic acid, or guanosine monophosphate (GMP), is a building block of RNA, an important component in the functioning of living cells, and is found in animals, plants and bacteria. It is used as a flavor enhancer in foods. Guanylic acid is often added to savory products such as stock cubes, ready-to-eat noodles and crisps. Guanylic acid can be isolated from sardines, but can also be produced in a vegan way from yeast. Major producers have indicated that they use vegan-produced guanylic acid.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_hemp_info">Hemp was one of the first plants to be spun into usable fiber 50,000 years ago. It can be refined into a variety of commercial items, including paper, textiles, clothing, biodegradable plastics, paint, insulation, biofuel, food, and animal feed.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_honey_info">Honey is the sweet substance made by honey bees from the nectar of flowers. Honey is removed from the hive by beekeepers. The bees receive sugar water in return. Just like honey, this is nice and sweet, but lacks important nutrients for the bee that honey contains. The sugar water weakens the bees; they become more susceptible to fungal infections, mites and viruses.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_inosine_monophosphate_info">Inosinic acid, or inosine monophosphate (IMP), is a substance that occurs naturally in both plants and animals and plays a role in the metabolism of cells. It is used as a flavor enhancer in foods. Inosinic acid is often added to savory products such as stock cubes, ready-to-eat noodles and chips. Inosinic acid can be isolated from meat and fish, but can also be produced in a vegan way. Major producers have indicated that they use vegan-produced inosinic acid.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_inosinic_acid_info">Inosinic acid, or inosine monophosphate (IMP), is a substance that occurs naturally in both plants and animals and plays a role in the metabolism of cells. It is used as a flavor enhancer in foods. Inosinic acid is often added to savory products such as stock cubes, ready-to-eat noodles and chips. Inosinic acid can be isolated from meat and fish, but can also be produced in a vegan way. Major producers have indicated that they use vegan-produced inosinic acid.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_potassium_ascorbate_info">Potassium ascorbate is the potassium salt of ascorbic acid (vitamin C). Ascorbic acid is a natural acid, present in almost all fruits and vegetables. It is obtained commercially by the bacterial fermentation of glucose followed by a chemical oxidation step. Ascorbic acid is used as an anti-oxidant and bread improver.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_potassium_guanylate_info">Potassium guanylate is a guanylic acid. Guanylic acid is a building block of RNA, an important component in the functioning of living cells and is found in animals, plants and bacteria. It is used as a flavor enhancer in foods. Guanylic acid is often added to savory products such as stock cubes, ready-to-eat noodles and crisps. Guanylic acid can be isolated from sardines, but can also be produced in a vegan way from yeast. Major producers have indicated that they use vegan-produced guanylic acid.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_potassium_lactate_info">Potassium lactate is the potassium salt of lactic acid. It is a natural acid produced by lactic acid bacteria in fermented products. Potassium lactate is commercially produced by bacterial fermentation of molasses or starch. Lactic acid and lactates are used as preservatives. It stabilizes anti-oxidants and pectins and is added to a variety of products including cheese, candy and ice cream to prevent dehydration.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_potassium_nitrate_info">Potassium nitrate (saltpetre) is the potassium salt of nitric acid and is used, among other things, in fertilizers, fireworks and as a preservative in meat. Although it can be made from animal remains, it is usually obtained from minerals.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_carmine_info">Carmine is a bright red dye made from beetles. It is often used to color food, cosmetics and textiles.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_buttermilk_info">Buttermilk is an end product of skimmed milk. A conversion from lactose to lactic acid takes place by means of lactic acid bacteria. This creates buttermilk.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cashmere_info">Cashmere is a fabric made from the fur of goats.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_cotton_info">Cotton is a natural fibre from cotton plants and is used to produce material for clothing and other textile products. </string>
    <string name="ingredient_keratin_info">Keratin is often added to hair products in order to repair damaged hair, and sometimes keep hair straight. Keratin comes from ground up animal hair, horns, hooves, and feathers. You can’t find keratine directly in a plant, but it can be synthesized from amino acids extracted from plants. This is rare, however.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_coconut_fiber_info">Coir or coconut fiber is a natural fiber extracted from the outer husk of coconut. It is used in products such as floor mats, doormats, brushes and mattresses.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_l_cysteine_info">L-Cysteine is an amino acid that is used as a bread improver. It is often made from goose and duck feathers. Increasingly, L-Cysteine is produced with the help of bacteria.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_l_cystine_info">L-Cystine is the oxidized form of the amino acid L-Cysteine. Both are used as a bread improver. L-Cysteine is often made from goose and duck feathers. Increasingly, L-Cysteine is produced with the help of bacteria.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lactitol_info">Lactitol is a synthetic sugar alcohol made from milk sugar (lactose), obtained from whey. It is common in bakery products and confectionery.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lactobacillus_info">Lactobacillus probiotics are generally vegan, as they are bacteria — not an animal product. However, the probiotics may be cultured with dairy.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lactose_info">Lactose is a sugar found in diary products.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_latex_info">Latex is made naturally (from a rubber tree) or synthetically (from petroleum). However, dipped latex products, such as condoms, balloons, and latex gloves, often use the milk protein casein in the production process. Casein is an animal product.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lecithin_info">Lecithin is a compound that occurs in every living organism because it is part of the cell wall of every cell. Lecithin for commercial use is extracted from soybeans, sunflower seeds, rapeseed and (nowadays relatively rare) egg yolk.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_linen_info">Linen is made from the fibers of the flax plant.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lyocell_info">Lyocell is a form of rayon. It consists of cellulose fibre. The fibre is used to make textiles for clothing and other purposes.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lysozyme_info">Lysozyme, or muramidase, is a food enzyme obtained from chicken egg protein.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_milk_info">There are different kinds of milk. Cow, goat, sheep, horse and buffalo milk are not vegan. Almond, cashew, oat, coconut and rice milks are.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_powdered_milk_info">Powdered milk, or dried milk, is a manufactured dairy product made by evaporating milk to dryness.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lactic_acid_info">Most lactic acid is vegan, as it primarily occurs during the natural fermentation process of plants or is man-made using plants.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_formic_acid_info">Formic acid (metanoic acid) occurs naturally in ants, but also in all kinds of fruit (apples, strawberries, raspberries), honey and nettles. It is obtained commercially from sulfuric acid, caustic soda and carbon monoxide and used as a preservative in soft drinks, candy and ice cream.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_modal_info">Modal is a type of rayon, a fabric made from plant cellulose.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_mono__and_diglycerides_of_fatty_acids_info">Fatty acid mono- and diglycerides are synthetic fats obtained from glycerol and natural fatty acids. The fatty acids can be of animal or vegetable origin. In practice, it is almost always vegetable fat.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_musk_info">Musk is extracted from the musk deer that lives in the Himalayas and Tibet. It is a strongly scented substance often used in perfume.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_sodium_ascorbate_info">Sodium ascorbate is the sodium salt of ascorbic acid (vitamin C). It is a widely used antioxidant and acidity regulator. Ascorbic acid is a natural acid, present in almost all fruits and vegetables. It is obtained commercially by bacterial fermentation of glucose followed by a chemical oxidation step. Ascorbic acid is used as an anti-oxidant and bread improver.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_sodium_formate_info">Sodium formate is obtained commercially from caustic soda and carbon monoxide and used as a preservative in, for example, fruit juice.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_disodium_guanylate_info">Disodium guanylate is a guanylic acid. Guanylic acid is a building block of RNA, an important component in the functioning of living cells and is found in animals, plants and bacteria. It is used as a flavor enhancer in foods. Guanylic acid is often added to savory products such as stock cubes, ready-to-eat noodles and crisps. Guanylic acid can be isolated from sardines, but can also be produced in a vegan way from yeast. Major producers have indicated that they use vegan-produced guanylic acid.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_sodium_lactate_info">Sodium lactate is the sodium salt of lactic acid. It is a natural acid produced by lactic acid bacteria in fermented products. Sodium lactate is commercially produced by bacterial fermentation of molasses or starch. Lactic acid and lactates are used as preservatives. It stabilizes anti-oxidants and pectins and is added to a variety of products including cheese, candy and ice cream to prevent dehydration.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_sodium_nitrite_info">Sodium nitrite is mainly used as a preservative in meat, fish and cheese.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_nisin_info">Nisin is a polypeptide (short protein) antibiotic produced by the cheese bacteria Lactococcus lactis. The bacteria is sometimes grown with the help of milk. Nisin is used as a preservative in, for example, cheese, cottage cheese, cream and canned fruit.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_pearls_info">Pearls are created by oysters. Most pearls are cultured. This means that an irritant is implanted into the oyster shell. Subsequently, the oysters coates the irritant with the crystalline substance nacre and the pearl is harvested.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_lard_info">Lard is animal fat, mainly from the pork belly. Lard is obtained by melting the bacon. What remains is the melted fat and non-meltable leftovers, the so-called cracklings. Lard can also come from suet.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_schellac_info">Shellac is a glazing agent made from the secretions of the female lac bug. In foods it is used as a wax coating and is known under the name E904. It is used with fruits, bonbons and candies. Shellac is also used in silicones, furniture wax, coatings and in the pharmaceutical industry.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_skatole_info">Skatol is an organic compound with a very strong and unpleasant odor. It occurs naturally in the feces of mammals and birds. It is an aroma substance that is used (in very small quantities) in the preparation of certain perfumes.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_soybeans_info">The soybean is a legume derived from the soybean plant, which is used as a raw material for many soy products.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_soy_lecithin_info">Lecithin is a compound that occurs in every living organism because it is part of the cell wall of every cell. Lecithin for commercial use is extracted from soybeans, sunflower seeds, rapeseed and (nowadays relatively rare) egg yolk.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_tallow_info">Tallow is animal fat derived from sheep and cattle. It is used in many cosmetic products, especially creams and lotions. It is a greasy substance that retains moisture.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_vanilla_info">Vanilla is a sweet, smooth aroma of which vanillin is the main ingredient. Vanilla can consist of both natural vanilla and vanillin. A vanilla-like flavor can be made with the use of castoreum, but this is rare.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_violoxanthin_info">Violoxanthin is a natural coloring agent (yellow) present in many plants. It is commercially isolated from violets.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_vitamin_b12_info">Vitamin B12 (cobalamin) is naturally only found in animal products. A shortage can cause irreversible complaints. It is therefore strongly recommended to take vitamin B12 supplements if you follow a (largely) plant-based diet. Vitamin B12 in supplements is often made by bacteria and therefore considered vegan.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_vitamin_d2_info">Vitamin D2 (ergocalciferol) is almost always vegan. The vegetable ergosterol is converted into ergocalciferol under the influence of UV light. Vitamin D2 can also be produced by fungi.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_vitamin_d3_info">Vitamin D3 (cholecalciferol) can be derived from an animal source (such as sheep’s wool) or a vegan-friendly source (lichen).</string>
    <string name="ingredient_whey_protein_info">Whey protein comes from whey, a by-product of cheese production.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_whey_info">Whey is a by-product of cheese production.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_whey_powder_info">Whey powder comes from whey, a by-product of cheese preparation.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_wool_info">Wool is a textile fibre that is obtained from the fleece, hide or fur from animals. These animals may include sheep, goats and alpacas. It is used to produce textiles.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_wool_fat_info">Wool fat (lanoline) is a yellowish sebum secreted by sebaceous glands on the skin of sheep.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_zeaxanthin_info">Zeaxanthin is a natural orange colorant. The natural coloring is found in green plant leaves such as spinach, in certain fruits such as oranges, and in egg yolks.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_seaweed_info">Seaweeds are plants that grow in the sea. They contain an impressive range of nourishing ingredients.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_silk_info">Silk fabrics are made from the silk that silkworms spin for the cocoon in which they turn into butterflies.</string>
    <string name="ingredient_sunflower_lecithin_info">Lecithin is a compound that occurs in every living organism because it is part of the cell wall of every cell. Lecithin for commercial use is extracted from soybeans, sunflower seeds, rapeseed and (nowadays relatively rare) egg yolk.</string>
</resources>